<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents type="revealCallOut2" className="m10c02s12">
	<transcript>
		<text path="" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width: 924px;margin-bottom:0px"><![CDATA[Emma didn’t consider Sandy’s privacy when setting up the fundraising site…]]></text>
	</contentText>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s12/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769" />
	</contentBackground>	
	 <contentBg style="width: 685px;" ></contentBg>
	<pageTitle style="width: 924px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 924px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Click on each individual. To read the next, click the X to close the text box.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click next to reconsider your decision and try again.]]></text>
	</instructionText>	
	<revealCallOutContent style="top:166px;">
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="238px" top="5px" left="256px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s12/btn1.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 58px;" ><![CDATA[Emma]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="90px" style="height: 241px;top: -229px;left: 256px;width: 722px;">
				<text><![CDATA[It was so easy to set up the fundraising site – I described what happened to Sandy — that she was in a terrible auto accident; her car was hit by another car in the middle of an intersection. I said she suffered a broken leg, which will require another surgery and a lot of physical therapy. I also talked about her possible brain injury, and how it could be a long time before Sandy might be well enough to return to work at Johnson Controls. I wanted people to know how dire the situation is for Sandy, so that they'll be motivated to donate to her fund.]]></text>						
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="238px" top="5px" left="502px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s12/btn2.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 58px;" ><![CDATA[Alfredo, a Johnson Controls employee]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="400px" style="height: 241px;top: -229px;left: 256px;width: 722px;">
				<text><![CDATA[I'm one of Emma's Facebook friends, and I saw the link to the fundraising site she created for Sandy. I know Emma meant well, but she really shouldn't have discussed Sandy’s medical condition on the site and shouldn’t have brought Johnson Controls into it. I felt like I had to do something, so I reported what I saw.]]></text>					
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="238px" top="5px" left="748px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s12/btn3.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 58px;" ><![CDATA[Jules, Human Resources Director]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="760px" style="height: 241px;top: -229px;left: 256px;width: 722px;">
				<text><![CDATA[An employee reported that Emma created a fundraising site and linked the story on Facebook, and that the site revealed Sandy’s private medical history.]]></text>			
				<text><![CDATA[It’s clear that Emma was just trying to help, but she should have thought through the consequences of her actions. We must always respect the privacy of others and should never share someone else’s personal information without their permission. ]]></text>			
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
	</revealCallOutContent>	
</contents>