<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents type="revealCallOut2" className="m09s05">
	<transcript>
		<text path="" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width:574px;font-size: 15px;margin-bottom:0px"><![CDATA[]]></text>
	</contentText>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s04/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
	</contentBackground>	
	 <contentBg style="padding:20px 20px 20px 20px" ></contentBg>
	<pageTitle style="width: 574px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 574px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Click on each individual. To read the next, click the X to close the text box.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Select Next to reconsider your decision and try again.]]></text>
	</instructionText>	
	<revealCallOutContent style="top:135px;" >
		<revealCallOut width="300px" height="175px" top="15px" left="370px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s04/img_01.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			<buttonText  style="height: 40px;" ><![CDATA[Emma]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="" style="height: 220px;top:-250px; display: block; left: 370px; width: 610px;line-height:20px;">			
				<text style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><![CDATA[At first, I was able to easily separate my work at Johnson Controls with my side job, and only worked as a broker on nights and weekends. But the real estate market is really hot right now, and I got busy so quickly.  So I thought the best way to handle it would be to take some time off as sick days and use any free moments I had at work to get my broker work done. Word even got around at the office about my side job and some colleagues are interested in buying now – I needed more time for all of it!  ]]></text>						
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="300px" height="175px" top="15px" left="679px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s04/img_02.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 40px;" ><![CDATA[Roger, Emma’s manager]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="" style="height: 255px;top: -250px; display: block; left: 370px; width: 610px;">
				<text style="margin-bottom: 0px;"><![CDATA[Emma's work has really suffered and she has taken quite a lot of sick days, yet never appears sick when she returns from time off. Other employees in the department complained that she wasn't taking her fair share of customer calls, was frequently out, and that people were constantly stopping by her desk. When I asked Emma for an explanation she told me about the work she was doing as a broker for her brother in law’s company. She should have talked to me earlier, before this became so disruptive. I had to have a frank discussion with her about my expectations while she is at work here. ]]></text>					
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
	</revealCallOutContent>	
</contents>