<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents className="m10c02s17">
	<transcript>
		<text path="" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>
	</transcript>
	 <contentBackground cName="" >		
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c02/m10c02s17/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[A group of employees in a  company office building.]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
    <contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
    <panelText>
		<text width="650px" height="auto" top="0px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[This story illustrates how important it is to protect personal information that you have access to of our employees, customers or business partners.]]></text> 
		<text width="650px" height="auto" top="10px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[Remember – always be guided by our three key privacy principles of Limit-Guard-Delete.]]></text> 
		<text width="650px" height="auto" top="20px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[<ol> <li><span class="fontBold">Limit</span> the amount of personal data you request or provide. Only request or provide the data you need for the essential and primary purpose you want to fulfill.</li> <li><span class="fontBold">Guard</span> the data from unauthorized processing, loss, damage or alteration. Control the access to and dissemination of the data.</li> <li><span class="fontBold">Delete</span> the data in a proper manner once you no longer need it. Prevent and stop hoarding records.</li> </ol>]]></text>
		<text width="650px" height="auto" top="30px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[Medical conditions and other sensitive personal data, such as sexual orientation, require even more protection than other personal data.]]></text>
		<text width="650px" height="auto" top="40px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[Personal data may be shared only with people who are authorized to see it, have a business need to know the information, and intend to use it for legitimate business purposes.]]></text>
	</panelText>	
	<pageTitle style="width: 650px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 650px;margin-top:50px" >
		<text ><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
</contents>