<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contents type="reveal2">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module1/m01s07"  id="0" ><![CDATA[It’s not enough to avoid conflicts of interest – we also must avoid even the appearance of a conflict. Let’s review a better way to handle these situations.]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width:635px;margin-bottom:0px;font-size:15px;" ><![CDATA[You've just heard from some people who perceived a conflict of interest. How could these situations have been handled better?]]></text>			
	</contentText>
	<pageTitle style="width: 635px;margin-bottom: 5px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 635px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Select each heading to learn more.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
	<contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s07/contentBackground.jpg" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
	<popupBackground>
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s07/img_01.png" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
	</popupBackground>
	<tabHolder style=""></tabHolder>
	<tabs style="" >
		<tab id="1" type="callOut" style="" >
			<tabName><![CDATA[Employment and hiring]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s07/popup1.png" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="">
				<text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[Carter perceives a conflict of interest because Anna’s brother works in HR and she was awarded a job that Carter had applied for.]]></text>
				<text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[Before Anna was ever up for a promotion, she and her brother both should have notified the company of the potential conflict. Her brother could have removed himself from any decisions related to Anna’s role at Johnson Controls. This would have helped ensure that the best candidate was selected for the promotion and ensure there was no cause for speculation about having an unbiased selection process.]]></text>
			</tabText>
		</tab>		
		<tab id="2" type="planeText" style="top: 77px;">
			<tabName><![CDATA[Vendor selection]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s07/popup2.png" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="">
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[A vendor perceives a conflict of interest because he has learned about a friendship between his contact and the other vendor selected for the job.]]></text>
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[It’s possible it was acceptable for John’s friend’s company to bid for work with Johnson Controls, and to win the bid if they are the best choice. ]]></text>
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[However, John should have notified the company of his conflict, and the vendor selection should have been managed by someone who didn’t have a personal interest in helping a specific vendor.]]></text>
				</tabText>
		</tab>		
		<tab id="3" type="planeText" style="top: 155px;">
			<tabName><![CDATA[Corporate opportunities]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s07/popup3.png"><![CDATA[]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="">
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[A client perceives a potential conflict because a Johnson Controls employee referred him to a company he later learned she had a personal investment in.]]></text>
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[Vinca should have never put herself or Johnson Controls in this position. ]]></text>
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[She has a responsibility to Johnson Controls to share any opportunities that arise during her work – and she certainly can’t take advantage of these opportunities to benefit herself. Vinca should not be working or investing in a company that could find itself competing with Johnson Controls. ]]></text>
				</tabText>
		</tab>
	</tabs>	
</contents>