<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents className="m01s03">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module1/m01s03" id="0"><![CDATA[How good are you at recognizing risky situations? Read this scenario and decide if it represents a conflict of interest.]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	 <contentBackground cName="" >		
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s03/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[An office]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
	<contentBg style="width: 1000px;right: 10px;top: 30px;padding: 0;" wtbgStyle="padding: 15px 15px;" ></contentBg>
	<pageTitle style=""></pageTitle>
	<contentText >
		<text style=""><![CDATA[Can you recognize a conflict of interest?  Decide whether or not the following situations present a potential conflict and should be disclosed:]]></text>
	</contentText>
	<instructionText style="">
		<text><![CDATA[Select Yes or No for each option then click on Submit.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on the question marks to learn more.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
	<optionContent style="width:720px;">
		<option answer="1,0" >
			<img width="80px" height="70px" path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s03/img01.png" ><![CDATA[Woman in an apron as if working at a bakery]]></img>
			<text style="width: 450px;"><![CDATA[Jennifer, a Johnson Controls employee, plans to work at her sister’s new bakery on the weekends – but this week she called in sick to help run the store for their Grand Opening.]]></text>			
		</option>
		<option answer="0,1" >
			<img width="80px" height="70px" path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s03/img02.png" ><![CDATA[Man in business clothes]]></img>
			<text style="width: 450px;" ><![CDATA[Alex, a procurement employee at Johnson Controls, thinks his friend Steve would be perfect for a job that’s open at the Company. He tells Steve about the job and suggests he complete the online application.]]></text>
		</option>
		<option answer="1,0" >
			<img width="80px" height="110px" path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s03/img03.png" ><![CDATA[Woman in business clothes, Middle Eastern descent]]></img>	
			<text style="width: 450px;" ><![CDATA[Basma is a quality engineer at Johnson Controls. A vendor she manages offers her a consulting opportunity. He says they are looking for help setting up the outgoing quality checks for a new product line they are creating for Johnson Controls. The vendor makes it clear that Basma can complete the work in the evenings or on weekends – outside of her regular work schedule.]]></text>	
		</option>
		<option answer="1,0" >
			<img width="80px" height="70px" path="content/images/ltr/module1/m01s03/img04.png" ><![CDATA[Man in business clothes]]></img>	
			<text style="width:450px;" ><![CDATA[Carl was responsible for selecting an IT vendor to support Johnson Controls on an important project. Earlier in the year, he made a sizable investment in his friend’s IT company and that company has now submitted a bid for the job.]]></text>	
		</option>
	</optionContent>
	<optionAnswer>
		<text><![CDATA[Yes]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[No]]></text>
	</optionAnswer>
	<buttonText >		
		<text style=""><![CDATA[SUBMIT]]></text>
	</buttonText>
	<feedback>
		<correct style="top: 115px;height: 166px;">
			<text style="padding-top: 50px;text-align: center;font-size: 20px;"><![CDATA[That’s correct.]]></text>		 
		</correct>
		<incorrect style="top: 90px;height: 166px;">
			<text style="padding-top: 32px;text-align: center;font-size: 20px;"><![CDATA[That’s not correct. ]]></text>			
			<text style="font-size: 16px;text-align: center;"><![CDATA[Click on the question marks to learn more.]]></text>			
		</incorrect>		
	</feedback>
	<optionInfo>
		<option arrowTopPosition="52px" style="">
			<text style=""><![CDATA[It is not a problem that Jennifer works at the bakery on weekends to help her sister. However, it does create a conflict if her commitment to her sister affects her job responsibilities at Johnson Controls, such as when she feigned illness and missed a day of work during the week in favor of helping out at the bakery.]]></text>			
		</option>
		<option arrowTopPosition="126px" style="">
			<text style=""><![CDATA[Even though Alex works in procurement, he has not used his position to help his friend get the job. It is acceptable for Alex to recommend that Steve complete the application online, as Steve will go through the same process that all other applicants will follow.]]></text>			
		</option>
		<option arrowTopPosition="220px" style="">
			<text style=""><![CDATA[Basma supervises the work of a vendor and she is now considering the offer to work with that vendor on the side. If both companies employ her, where does her loyalty lie? There is potential for her to be conflicted, and such situations need to be avoided. At a minimum, Basma needs to disclose the potential conflict of interest.]]></text>			
		</option>
		<option arrowTopPosition="315px" style="">
			<text style=""><![CDATA[Carl stands to benefit financially if the company he has invested in wins the bid. His personal connection to the decision could affect his ability to make an unbiased decision, making this a conflict of interest.]]></text>			
		</option>				
	</optionInfo>
</contents>