<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents type="revealCallOut2" className="m05s11">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module5/m05s11" id="0" ><![CDATA[If you export anything for Johnson Controls, you need to strictly comply with the trade requirements. Select each heading to ensure you know what to do.]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width: 924px;margin-bottom:0px"><![CDATA[To comply with trade requirements, you will need to:]]></text>
	</contentText>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module5/m05s11/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[Woman obtaining required authorization]]></img>
	</contentBackground>	
	 <contentBg style="padding: 20px 20px 20px 20px;" ></contentBg>
	<pageTitle style="width: 924px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 924px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Select each heading. To read the next, click the X to close the text box.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>	
	<revealCallOutContent style="top: 170px;" >
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="210px" top="15px" left="20px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module5/m05s11/btn1.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Woman obtaining required authorization]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height:78px" ><![CDATA[Obtain any required authorizations]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="90px" style="height: 210px;top: -215px;width:958px;">
				<text><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Ensure you know which controlled goods, technology, software and services require authorization to be exported, including dual-use items – this helps ensure that these items only go to countries and end users who are authorized to receive them.</li> <li>Strictly follow any authorizations you receive (e.g. identified parties, quantity and value) and hold any business partners to the same standard.</li> </ul>]]></text>					
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="210px" top="15px" left="263px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module5/m05s11/btn2.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[A Globe]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height:78px" ><![CDATA[Avoid restricted end users, end uses and destinations]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="400px" style="height: 210px;top: -215px;width:958px;">
				<text><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Ensure you know which trade controls restrict or prohibit exports to which countries, individuals or entities.</li> <li>Find out which end uses are also restricted.</li> <li>Be aware that restricted entities and individuals are identified by governmental agencies on a variety of lists and are typically referred to as “restricted parties”.</li> <li>If you are responsible for conducting restricted party screening, ensure you complete it as required using the Johnson Controls software tool.</li> </ul>]]></text>						
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="210px" top="15px" left="505px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module5/m05s11/btn3.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Syrian Flag]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height:78px" ><![CDATA[Follow regulatory restrictions and Johnson Controls procedures]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="760px" style="height: 280px;top: -215px;width:958px;">
				<text><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Do not engage in any transactions that involve: <ul> <li>Iran</li> <li>North Korea</li> <li>Syria</li> <li>Cuba</li> <li>Sudan</li> <li>Crimea Peninsula region of Ukraine*</li> </ul></li> </ul>]]></text>			
				<text><![CDATA[*As Crimea is not well defined, consult with our trade compliance experts before doing any business with Russia or the Ukraine.]]></text>			
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="210px" top="15px" left="747px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module5/m05s11/btn4.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Employee on computer reporting a request to a trade compliance expert]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height:78px" ><![CDATA[Do not participate in unsanctioned boycotts]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText showHeader="true" arrowleft="760px" style="height: 210px;top: -215px;width:958px;">
				<text><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Be aware that restrictive trade requests can be subtle – like being asked to abide by boycotting countries' laws.</li> <li>Restrictive trade requests can be received from anyone, anywhere in the world, so be diligent in your review of business documents, letters of credit and correspondence.</li> <li>If you receive a request that appears to be a restrictive trade request, do not respond to it; instead, report it to a trade compliance expert.</li> </ul>]]></text>			
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
	</revealCallOutContent>	
</contents>