<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents className="m10c03s29">
	<transcript>
		<text path="" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>
	</transcript>
	 <contentBackground >		
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c03/m10c03s29/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
	 <contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
    <panelText>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="0px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[When offering or accepting gifts or entertainment, always be sure to use good judgment, discretion and moderation.]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="10px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[Gifts given or received should:]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="20px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[<ul> <li>be modest in value, so that they cannot reasonably be expected to affect the receiver’s independent judgment</li> <li>be infrequent, and never tied to a potential contract or business</li> <li>never be cash or cash equivalents, such as gift cards</li> <li>never look or feel like a bribe</li> </ul>]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="30px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[The threshold for reporting gifts is USD$200. If you receive anything valued at or over USD$200, report it using a gift form on <a href="http://complianceforms.jci.com" target="_blank" class="aLinkColor">http://complianceforms.jci.com</a>]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="40px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[The disclosure will be reviewed and you'll be told whether or not you can accept the gift.]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="50px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName=""><![CDATA[Any entertainment offered or accepted should serve a business purpose and not be offensive or culturally inappropriate.]]></text>
		<text width="860px" height="auto" top="60px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="0 0 60px 0" cName=""><![CDATA[If you attend business entertainment events, you are representing Johnson Controls. In that capacity, you should not drink alcohol excessively and you should never be associated with venues offering sexually explicit adult entertainment, which is inappropriate for business-related events.]]></text>
	</panelText>	
	<pageTitle style="width: 860px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 860px;" >
		<text ><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
</contents>