<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents className="m10c01s26 verticallyCenterPageData">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module10/m10c01/m10c01s26" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>
	</transcript>
	 <contentBackground >		
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c01/m10c01s26/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[A gift.]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
	 <contentBg style="width: 880px;top: 30px;right: 30px;" ></contentBg>
    <panelText>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="0px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[When offering or accepting gifts or entertainment, always be sure to use good judgment, discretion and moderation.]]></text>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="10px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[Gifts given or received should:<ul> <li>be modest in value, so that they cannot reasonably be expected to affect the receiver’s independent judgment</li> <li>be infrequent, and never tied to a potential contract or business or given/accepted in a time frame that is close to a negotiation</li> <li>never be cash or cash equivalents, such as gift cards</li> <li>never look or feel like a bribe</li> </ul>]]></text>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="20px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[The threshold for reporting gifts is USD$200. If you receive anything valued at USD$200 or more, report it using a gift form on <a href="http://complianceforms.jci.com" target="_blank" class="aLinkColor">http://complianceforms.jci.com</a>. ]]></text>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="30px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[The disclosure will be reviewed and you'll be told whether or not you can accept the gift.]]></text>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="40px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[Any entertainment offered or accepted should not be offensive or culturally inappropriate. If you attend business entertainment events, you are representing Johnson Controls. In that capacity, you should not drink alcohol excessively and you should never be associated with venues offering sexually explicit entertainment, which is inappropriate for business related events.]]></text>
		<text width="100%" height="auto" top="50px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="0 0 50px 0" cName="" fontSize="15px"><![CDATA[Remember that there are stricter rules when dealing with government officials. Any gift to a government official must be pre-approved by submitting a request in advance at <a href="http://complianceforms.jci.com" target="_blank" class="aLinkColor">http://complianceforms.jci.com</a>.]]></text>
	</panelText>	
	<pageTitle style="width: 100%;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 700px;" >
		<text ><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
</contents>