<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents className="m10c01s07">
	<transcript>
		<text path="" id="0" ><![CDATA[]]></text>
	</transcript>
	 <contentBackground cName="" >		
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module10/m10c01/m10c01s07/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[Data Security Background]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
    <contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
    <panelText>
		<text width="620px" height="auto" top="0px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[You are always responsible for protecting the physical and digital security of all personal and confidential information in your possession. Remember to follow the golden rules for Data Privacy: Limit-Guard-Delete.]]></text> 
		<text width="620px" height="auto" top="10px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[<ol> <li><span class="fontBold">Limit</span> the amount of personal data you request or provide. Only request or provide the data you need for the essential and primary purpose you want to fulfill.</li> <li><span class="fontBold">Guard</span> the data from unauthorized processing, loss, damage or alteration. Control the access to and dissemination of the data.</li> <li><span class="fontBold">Delete</span> the data in a proper manner once you no longer need it. Prevent and stop hoarding records.</li> </ol>]]></text> 
		<text width="620px" height="auto" top="20px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="" cName="" ><![CDATA[Ensure that there is one system of record for master data files and do not work from a local copy unless you are certain you have the most recent version. Once finished, you should delete it from your local drive.]]></text>
		<text width="620px" height="auto" top="30px" position="relative" left="0px" padding="0 0 30px 0" cName="" ><![CDATA[Personal and confidential data of customers, employees and business partners can be shared only with people who are authorized to see it and have a legitimate business need for the information.]]></text>
	</panelText>	
	<pageTitle style="width: 620px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 620px;" >
		<text ><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
</contents>