<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contents type="reveal2">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module2/m02s13"  id="0" ><![CDATA[Government business often involves special laws, regulations and obligations, especially in regard to gifts and entertainment. Select each heading to learn more.]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width:635px;margin-bottom:0px;font-size:15px;" ><![CDATA[When dealing with government officials:]]></text>			
	</contentText>
	<pageTitle style="width: 635px;margin-bottom: 5px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 635px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Select each heading.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>
	<contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/contentBackground.jpg" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[International Flags]]></img>
	</contentBackground>
	<popupBackground>
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/img_01.png" ><![CDATA[]]></img>
	</popupBackground>
	<tabHolder style="height: 394px;"></tabHolder>
	<tabs style="" >
		<tab id="1" type="callOut" style="" >
			<tabName><![CDATA[Be sure you know how to identify government officials]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/popup1.png" ><![CDATA[Government Officials]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="width: 350px;height: 368px;">
				<text style="font-size:14px;line-height:18px"><![CDATA[A government official is an officer or employee of any entity controlled by a government, including political office holders and managers of state-owned enterprises.]]></text>
				<text style="font-size:14px;line-height:18px"><![CDATA[Government officials include, for example:]]></text>
				<text style="font-size:14px;line-height:20px"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Elected or appointed officials in any level of government</li> <li>Candidates for political office and political party officials</li> <li>Officers or employees of public international organizations</li> <li>Employees of state agencies, such as customs officials or police</li> <li>Employees of state-controlled enterprises, such as utility companies</li> <li>Employees of government-owned institutions, such as universities or hospitalities</li> <li>Military personnel</li> </ul>]]></text>
			</tabText>
		</tab>		
		<tab id="2" type="planeText" style="top: 32px;">
			<tabName><![CDATA[Seek approval first]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/popup2.png" ><![CDATA[Employee following approval process]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="height: 368px;">
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Always obtain approval from the Law department or the Compliance team before using gifts or entertainment to build relationships with current or prospective government customers.</li> <li>Don’t offer or provide anything of value to a government third party with the intention of seeking to influence the official to provide a benefit to Johnson Controls.</li> </ul>]]></text>
				</tabText>
		</tab>		
		<tab id="3" type="planeText" style="top: 64px;">
			<tabName><![CDATA[Understand the gift rules]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/popup3.png"><![CDATA[Government Official]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="height: 368px;">
				 <text><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Ensure that gifts to government officials are legal, reasonable and recorded properly and accurately.</li> <li>Any gift to a government official must be pre-approved by submitting a request in advance at <a href="http://complianceforms.jci.com" target="_blank" class="aLinkColor">http://complianceforms.jci.com</a></li> <li>Don’t give a gift to a government official close to the submission of a public tender proposal.</li> <li>Don’t give a gift to a government official while regulatory approvals or decisions are pending, when the official has a role or influence in the decision.</li> </ul>]]></text>
				</tabText>
		</tab>	
		<tab id="4" type="planeText" style="top: 107px;">
			<tabName><![CDATA[Understand the entertainment rules]]></tabName>
			<buttonImg path="" ><![CDATA[]]></buttonImg>
			<backgroungImg >				
				<img path="content/images/ltr/module2/m02s13/popup4.png"><![CDATA[Employee filling out approval forms]]></img>
			</backgroungImg>
			<tabText style="height: 368px;">
				 <text style="font-size:15px;"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Special rules apply to entertainment involving government officials. Please check the Delegation of Authority (DoA) matrix for your business and ensure you comply with the monetary thresholds and approval process required if you are entertaining government clients.</li> <li>Don’t offer a gift or entertainment to a government third party while decisions are pending regarding contracts or regulatory approvals, when the official has a role or influence in the decision.</li> <li>All entertainment of U.S. Federal Government employees must be pre-approved.</li> <li>The AB pre-approval form is available at <a href="http://complianceforms.jci.com/" target="_blank" class="aLinkColor">http://complianceforms.jci.com</a></li> </ul>]]></text>
				</tabText>
		</tab>
	</tabs>	
</contents>