<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<contents type="revealCallOut2" className="m03s09">
	<transcript>
		<text path="audio/module3/m03s09" id="0" ><![CDATA[So, you know bribery is bad, but what about facilitation payments? Let’s get some managers’ advice on this one.]]></text>		
	</transcript>
	<contentText >
		<text style="width: 924px;margin-bottom:0px"><![CDATA[Facilitation payments are low-value, unofficial fees paid to public officials to encourage them to do their job properly or promptly. Should you pay them? ]]></text>
	</contentText>
	<contentBackground >
		<img path="content/images/ltr/module3/m03s09/contentBackground.jpg"  minwidth="769"><![CDATA[Empty Office Background]]></img>
	</contentBackground>	
	 <contentBg style="" ></contentBg>
	<pageTitle style="width: 924px;"></pageTitle>
	<instructionText style="width: 924px;" >
		<text><![CDATA[Click on each manager to get his or her advice.]]></text>
		<text><![CDATA[Click on Next (bottom right arrow) to continue.]]></text>
	</instructionText>	
	<revealCallOutContent style="top: 174px;">
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="172px" top="15px" left="20px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module3/m03s09/btn1.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Male employee]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 40px;"><![CDATA[Jorge]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText arrowleft="90px" style="height: 145px;top: -27px;line-height:20px;">
				<text><![CDATA[Johnson Controls’ policy prohibits facilitation or “grease” payments. Never make a facilitation payment, even if it’s a small amount. If someone asks you to pay a facilitation fee, you should refuse and report the incident to your manager and the Law Department right away.]]></text>	<text><![CDATA[The only exception is if you believe your health or safety may be in danger if you do not pay. However, you must report any such payments to your manager and a member of the Law Department, Compliance or Enterprise Security team as soon as possible. ]]></text>						
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="172px" top="15px" left="263px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >			
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module3/m03s09/btn2.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Female employee]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 40px;"><![CDATA[Li]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText arrowleft="400px" style="height: 95px;top: -27px;">
				<text><![CDATA[In some countries, facilitation payments are part of doing business, but that doesn’t make them right. Public officials shouldn’t abuse their power for personal gain. Facilitation payments create an unfair playing field, where some people are denied a license or service they need just because they don’t have the cash to pay unofficial fees. Don’t buy into that unjust system.]]></text>					
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="172px" top="15px" left="505px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module3/m03s09/btn3.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Female employee]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 40px;"><![CDATA[Monica]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText arrowleft="760px" style="height: 145px;top: -27px;">
				<text style=""><![CDATA[It’s important to be prepared in case someone asks you for a facilitation payment. Sometimes public officials ask for them, and it can be difficult to refuse. In the past, some companies allowed these payments, seeing them as an unfortunate requirement of doing business in certain countries. But now some anti-bribery laws – like the UK Bribery Act – prohibit facilitation payments, and Johnson Controls has made a decision not to allow them in our business. So, unless your physical safety, health or liberty is at stake, don’t pay them!]]></text>			
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
		<revealCallOut width="230px" height="172px" top="15px" left="749px" ticktop="5px" tickleft="3px" >
			<img path="content/images/ltr/module3/m03s09/btn4.png" minwidth="769" ><![CDATA[Male employee]]></img>
			<buttonText style="height: 40px;"><![CDATA[Vihaan]]></buttonText>
			<popupArrow style=""/>
			<popText arrowleft="760px" style="height: 120px;top: -27px;">
				<text><![CDATA[Remember that not all payments are facilitation payments. Some payments made to expedite a process are legitimate. For example, in many countries, you can pay an additional fee to receive a passport more quickly. If there is a publicly available schedule of fees, then those payments are not facilitation fees and are okay to pay. Just make sure that you receive a receipt that accurately describes the payment made, and always record it appropriately in your expense report.]]></text>				
			</popText>
		</revealCallOut>
		
	</revealCallOutContent>	
</contents>